Guide to the Center for Jewish Living records, 1985-2015.
Center for Jewish Living records
- Alpha Subject Files
  - McGrogan, Victoria (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - McHugh, Matthew, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - McKeith, D Evan, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - McMillian, Robert, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Mead, JP, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Mehta, Yufen Lee, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Meislahn, Nancy, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Menter, Rudin and Trivelpiece, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Meranus, Philip, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Don Meriliahti Construction, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Mernick, Stephen, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Meshorer, Marc, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Mesorah Publications, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Messit, Michael, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Metzer, Rabbi Yona, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Meyda Stained Glass Studio, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Meyer, Anne F, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - University of Miami, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Mickelberry Co., 1987 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Miller, Arlene, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Miller, Philip, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Millet, Ruvain, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - US Mills, Inc, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Milstein, Howard, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Minsk, Seth Samson (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Mintz, Rabbi Etan, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Minwax Co (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Mish, Risa, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Mizelle, Chad, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Modular Comfort Systems, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Moller, Marc, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Monclova, Blodwen (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Mond, Alan, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Monroe, James (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Monroe Kitchen Equipment, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Montal, Mickey, 2010-2012 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Moore, Kevin D, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Moriah, Avner, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Morley, Jr, James E, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Moss, Morris and Lilian, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Moss, Samuel, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Mother's food products, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Moynihan, Daniel, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Muscente, Paul, 2012-2015 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Muschel, Bernard, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Muss, Steven, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Mydans, Carl, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Naftel, Richard, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Na'Amat USA Women's Labor Zionist, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Naider, Fred, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Nash, Jack, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - National Council of Young Israel, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Nelson, sam, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Niederkorn, Tom, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Netanyahu, Benzion, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Neusner, Noam, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Newhouse, SI, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Newman, Diane, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Newman, Robert M, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Nguyen, True, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Nissan Motor Corp, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Noel, J Andrew, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Nichols, Alan H, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Nie, Yunan, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Noden, Stephen, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Northeast Group Credit Services, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Norstar Bank of Upstate NY, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Noto, Anthony, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Novick, Barry Roy and Barbara Goldman, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Oblak, Janiece Bacon, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - O'brien, John (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Ocean Spray Cranberries Inc, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - O'Connor, Sandra Day (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Odd, Melvin, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - O'Dowd, Ryan, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Oestreich Foundation, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Okon, Joseph J, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Olsen, Harold P, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - Olson, Todd and Lesky, 2012-2015 (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - Oppenheimer, Ellen, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - Oppenheimer, Koby, 1998, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - Ori, Amos, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - Orefice, Stu, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 117)
  - Orkin and Bennett, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - Osborne, Michelle, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - Osgood, Dean Russell, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - Oskinsky, Michael, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Orthodox Union, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - Ostrom, John S, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 123)
  - Ossman, Hal and Rachel, 2011-2015 (Box 10, Folder 124)
  - Ostrow, Joseph, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 125)
  - Ovadiah, Janice, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 126)
  - Owen, David, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 127)
  - Paese, Dennis, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Paleen, William, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Palmer, Carol True (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - Paracelsian, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - Parker, Alfred and Regina (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - Parnes, Aaron D, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - The Paris Agency, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - Passover, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - Passover, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - Passover, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 137)
  - Passover, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - Passover, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Passover, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - Passover, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - Passover, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Passover, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Passover, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Payroll and Honorariums (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Peacock, Dawne, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Pearse, Deborah, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Pekelner, Alan, 1988-1991, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Peltz, Nelson, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - Penalver, Dean Eduardo, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - Perceptions, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 152)
  - Perez, Hector, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - Perman, Paul and Edith, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 154)
  - Peromsik, Aaron, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 155)
  - Perrier Group, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 156)
  - Peters, Earl and Harriet, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 157)
  - Peterson, Carolyn, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 158)
  - Petrie, Milton, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 159)
  - Philipp Brothers, Inc, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 160)
  - Pietrafesa, Gerard, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 161)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 162)
  - Piotrowski, Aliza (Box 10, Folder 163)
  - Pirow, Josh, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 164)
  - Pischel, Ernest, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 165)
  - PO Box 363, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 166)
  - Podwal, Mark (Box 10, Folder 167)
  - Polak, Samuel, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 168)
  - M Polaner, Inc, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 169)
  - Polansky, Bill, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 170)
  - Polenberg, Richard, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 171)
  - Polevoy, Joshua, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 172)
  - Polevoy, Lazar, 2013, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 173)
  - Polevoy, Richard, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 174)
  - Pomeranz, Larry, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 175)
  - Poole, Cheryl C., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 176)
  - Popkin, Elsie Dinsmore (Box 10, Folder 177)
  - Portable Feast, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 178)
  - Possen, Uri, 1990, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 179)
  - Potamkin, Victor, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 180)
  - Poyurs, Yeshaya, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 181)
  - Prager, Dennis, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 182)
  - Prero, Rabbi Samuel, 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 183)
  - The Prince Co, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 184)
  - Princeton University (Box 10, Folder 185)
  - Proposal Viability, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 186)
  - Propp, Mortimer, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 187)
  - Rabkin, Jeremy (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Radinsky, Rabbi David, 2002-2005 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Radinsky, Joseph, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Ramin, Richard, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Rapfogel, William, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Randel, Don M, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Rauker, Marty, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Rawlings, Hunter R, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Raynar, Scot, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Reagan, President Ronald, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Redfern, Elwin, 2011-2015 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Reese, Jean, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Regenstein, Joe M, 1988-1990, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Reich, Walter, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Reichmann, Paul, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Reigle, Joan, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Reichenback, Inge T, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Reitenbach, Nicholas, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Rendsburg, Gary, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Rehnquist, William, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Relihan, Walter, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Reppy, Judith, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Resnick, Josh, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Reutlinger, Shlomo (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Reynolds, Hugh, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - RFK Center, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Rheins, Dr. Carl, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Rhodes, Frank H T, 1987-1992 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Rich, Marc, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Rich Products Corp., 1988 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Rideout, Blanchard, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Rifkin, Ruth, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Riley, Michael, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Riley, Naomi Schaefer, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Riskin, Greg, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Rith, Maude, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Robert Theodore Assoc. Inc, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Roberts, Jeri M, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Roberts, Michael, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Robinson, St. John, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Roberts, Steve, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Robinson, Sonja, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Rockoff, Stuart, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Rockwell, Kay L, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Rogers, Frederick, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - I. Rokeach and Sons, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Roscoe, Lewis S, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Rose, Richard, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Rosen, Sharon Maza, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Rosenbaum, Beverly and Brock, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Rosenbaum, Howard, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Rosenbaum, Richard, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Rosenberg, Abraham, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Rosenberg, Edgar, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Rosenberg, Howard, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Rosenberg and Stiebel, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Rosenfeld, Allison, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Rosenfeld, Irene, 2005-2009 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Rosenfield, Leonard, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Rosengarten, Dale, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Rosenkranz, Joshua, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Rosenthal, AM, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Rosenthal, Rabbi Ed, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Rosenthal, Ellen Cohen, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Rosenthal, John and Josh, 2005, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Rosenthal, Leah (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Rosh, Joel and Susan, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Ross, Ben Moshe, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Ross, Betsy McCaughey, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Ross, Dennis B (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Ross, Lisa, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Roth, Lawrence, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Ross, Rabbi Josh, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Roth, Nelson, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Roth, Sharon, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Rothman Foundation, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Rothman, Henry I, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Routman, Aron and Joan Faier, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Royal Wine, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Rubinstein, Sam, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Ruchlin, Ari, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Louis and Rachel Rudin Foundation Inc, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Ruffer, Paul, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Rumney, Timothy, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Russell, Stephen, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Russo, Johnny, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Ryger, Jack (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Sabba, Daniel, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Sablich, Peter, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Safdie, Gabriel, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Safe Haven Museum, 2011, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Saferstein, Sheila, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Sagan, Carl, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Salas-Castro, Alvaro, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Salino, Catherine C, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Sallie Mae, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Salmon, Henry and Linda, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Sandelman, Robert, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Sanders, James, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Sanders, Steven D, 1990-1991, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Sandler, Chad, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Sandoz Nutrition, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Sands, Marvin, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - Sanua, Marianne (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - Santoro, Thomas, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Saperstein, Adina, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - Saperstein, Nathan, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Sarkany, Andrea, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Sarna, Aaron, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - David Sarnoff Research Center, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Savannah Jewish Archives, 2004, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Sasto, Dorienne I, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Sayward, Nicole, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Sax, Steve, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Schaap, Jeremy (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Schaap, Noam, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Scalia, Antonin, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Schectman, Richard and Devera, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - Scheff, Matthew, 2011-2012 (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - Scheuer Family Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - Schildkraut, Carl (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - Schmidt, Deb Thyng, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Schoefield, Fannie G, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Schoenfeld, Shelly D, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Schlussel, Marc, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Schlussel, Mark E, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 126)
  - Schilowitz, Alan, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 127)
  - Scheinfeld, Ellen, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 128)
  - Schenkel, Edna, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - Schindler, Alexander, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - Schirman, Tamar, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 131)
  - Schnapp, Gary, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - Schneider, Harry, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - Schneider, Paul, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - Scholet-Eligator, Elora, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - Schorr, Nathaniel, 2011-2012 (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - Schulman, Larry, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Schuster, Hillel, 1994, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Schuster, Marilyn (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Schwab, Stewart, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - Schwartz, Larry, 2008, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - Schwartz, Howard, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - Schwartz, Samuel, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Schneider, Stephanie, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - Schwartzberg, Nathan, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - Schrader, Kurt, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - Scot, A, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Scott, Gwen, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Season Products Corporation, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Sechler, Stephanie, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Seebach, Michell, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Segal, Michael, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Seiden, Jack, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Semel, Jessica Bell, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Seneca Foods Corporation, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Sephardic Orgs. (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Shalom, Stephen, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Shames, Jonathan, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Shao, Irene, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Shapiro, Gavriel, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - Schultz, Karen, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - Shah, Alan, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Shapero, Alex (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - Shapiro, Linda A, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - Shapiro, Edwin, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - Sharansky, Natan, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - Sharp, Kevin, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - Shepard, Cathy Goldrich, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - Sher, Neal M (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - Shiran, Haim, 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 170)
  - Shorofsky, Morris, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 171)
  - Shoulson, Rivka, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - Shmidman, Lisa, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Shribman, David, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - Shuchatowitz, Joseph, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - Shulman, Gideon, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 176)
  - Shulman, Rywka and Nisson, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 177)
  - Shumate, Ann, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 178)
  - Siegal, Burton, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 179)
  - Sidon, Karol, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 180)
  - Siegel, Judy Fried, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 181)
  - Siegel, Mark Alan, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 182)
  - Siegel, Martin, 1990, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 183)
  - Siegel, Rochell, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 184)
  - Siegel, Seth M, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 185)
  - Seisser, Ron, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 186)
  - Silber, Jessica, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 187)
  - Silbert, Marc and Peggy, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 188)
  - Silett, Beverly, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 189)
  - Silver, Rabbi Avi, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 190)
  - Silverman, Irving T, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 191)
  - Silverman, Jeffrey S, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 192)
  - Simon, Andrea B, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 193)
  - Simckes, Seymour (Box 11, Folder 194)
  - Singh, Kirat, 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 195)
  - Sioux Honey Association, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 196)
  - Sirlin, Deanna, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 197)
  - Sitlington, James R, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 198)
  - Skorton, David J, 2012-2015 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Slade, Debbie, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Slonin, Efrat, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Small, Mary, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Small, Wilson, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Murray, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Sanford L, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Smith, William, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - JM Smucker Co, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Smyck and Smyck, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Snell, Barbara, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Snider, Alfred, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Sniderman, Debbie (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Snyder, Lee, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Soclof, Rachel, 2012, 2016 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Harny Sokol Memorial, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Solomon, David, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Solomon Equities, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Solomon, Karey, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Solomon, Richard, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Soloveichik, Rabbi Meir, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Some, Norman Mark, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Somkin, Fred and Bodil, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Sommer, Ted, 1990, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Southeast Asia Program at Cornell, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Spar, Theodore, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Speiser, Abraham, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Speizer, Rabbi Kale, 2010-2012 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Sperling, Anne, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Sperling, Randall, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Spiegel, Inc, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Spitz, Laura, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Stage, Patricia E (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Stahl, Charles W, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Stahl, Shai, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Star-Kist Foods Inc, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Starr, Greg, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Starr, Robert and Barbara, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Stein, Barry and Susan, 2013, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Stein, Daniel, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Steinberg Foundation, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Steinberg, Rabbi Leonard, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Stein-Dove, Cathy, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Steinfels, Peter, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Stephens, Maura, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Stern, Ernest, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Stern, Steven, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Steuer, Deborah, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Steuer, Jill, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Stevens, Patrick, 2011-2015 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Stillman, Norman, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Stinson Canning Co, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - St. John, Oberdorf, Williams, Edington, and Curtin, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Stolper, Rabbi Pinchas (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Stone, Aaron, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Stone, Carole, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Stone, Irving I, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Stone, Peter, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Storck, Morris, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Storrier, John E, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Strassberg, Michael, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Strassler, David H, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Strauss, Barry, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Strauss, Marcy, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Streiter, Aaron and Janet, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Strelitz, Leonard, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Strickman, Norman, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Strongwater, Andrea, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Strossen, Nadine, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Striebel, Abigail, 1989-1992 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Strudler, Robert J, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Student Agencies, 2012-2015 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Sucari, Rafael, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Sues, Jared, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Sugin, Amy, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Sultanik, David, 1991, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - SUNY Binghamton Hillel, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Surrender of Lease- CJL to CU, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Sweetman, Susan, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Swergold, Gary, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Swergold, Perry, 2011-2013 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Swieringa, Robert, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Sumitomo Bank, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Suracase Herald American, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Surkin, Marie, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Szekely, Yoran and Beatrice, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Tanner, George and Judith, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Tanner, Harold (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Target National Bank, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Tarr, Curtis W, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Taubman, Alfred, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Teicher, Martin, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Teitelbaum, Lisa, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Temel, Charles, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Tenenbaum, Morris (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Thalassinos, Pablo, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Thaler and Thaler, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Thomas, Clarence, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Thomas, Joe (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Thomas, Sarah, 2006, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - SB Thomas, Inc, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Tisch, James, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Tisch, Laurence A, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Todd, Jacob L, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Tompkins County Chamber of Commerce, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Tompkins Trust Co, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Torricelli, Robert, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Total Business Financial Consultants, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Treman and Clynes, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Tribe, Lawrence, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - Tropper, David, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - Troy, Aaron, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - Trump, Donald J, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Tuch Foundation, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - Turk, Jeffery, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Turkish, Elsie, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Turkish, Sid, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Twitter, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Uhlmann Co, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Ulrich, Clare, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Uris, Leon, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 121)
  - US Department of Interior, Secretary, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - US Air Group Inc, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - Vacco, Dennis C, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - Van Gorden, Judith, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - Van Munching and Co, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - Velazquez, Rhonda, 2012-2013 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - Verity, Kelli, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - Victor, Sarah, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - Vine, Deborah, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - Vlasic Foods Ind., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - Vlock, Laurel F, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Wachtler, Sol, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Wagyu Beef Dinner, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Walker, Edward S, 2005, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - Wallach, Steven, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - Ward, Milton Hood, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - Ware, W Barlow, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 138)
  - Warren, Joey, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 139)
  - Wayne, Barrett, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 140)
  - Wealcatch, William, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - Weaver, Jeremy, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 142)
  - Wechsler, Robert, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 143)
  - Wechsler, Skirnick, Harwood, Halebian and Feffer, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 144)
  - Wecker, Johm, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 145)
  - Weidenbaum, Murray, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 146)